Guide to the Frank Lyon Polk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject Files, 1912-(1915-1921); Series III; 7 linear feet (7 boxes)
  - Germany
    - Legal papers and correspondence with the Department of Justice re: Paul Koenig, 1915 December 23 - 1916 January 24 (Box 25, Folder 277)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1915, undated (Box 25, Folder 278)
    - List of dossiers re: controversies with the Central Powers, [1915?] (Box 25, Folder 279)
    - Correspondence re: relations between the Berwind-White Coal Company and the Hamburg American Line, 1916 January 8 - February 11 (Box 25, Folder 280)
    - Charles Warren: "Recommendations to the Attorney General as to Course to be pursued relative to German Merchant Vessels in Ports of the United States at the present time, or in case of outbreak of War" (carbon), 1917 February 3 (Box 25, Folder 281)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: German insurance companies in the U.S., 1917 March 30 - August 4 (Box 25, Folder 282)
    - Memorandum re: regulation of German, financial interests in the United States (carbon), [1917 Apr?] (Box 25, Folder 283)
    - William Bayard Hale's suppressed article, "An Evening with the German Emperor" (1909), and related memoranda and cables about its publication, 1917 December 21 - 1918 February 2 (Box 25, Folder 284)
    - Memoranda re: civilian communication with Germany, 1918 February 12, March 1 (Box 25, Folder 285)
    - French High Commission to the United States: memorandum re: growth of the German Army, 1914-1918 (original and translation), 1918 October 15 (Box 25, Folder 286)
    - French High Commission to the United States: translation of German order, 1918 Sep 5, for destruction in occupied areas (original and translation), [1918 September 5 - October 28] (Box 25, Folder 286)
    - Danish article re: the German diplomatic service (translated copy, supplied by the American Legation, Copenhagen), 1918 October 23 (Box 25, Folder 287)
    - Department of State: Diplomatic Correspondence between the Governments of the United States and Germany, 1918 October 23 (Box 25, Folder 288)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: extradition and trial of Kaiser Wilhelm, 1918 November 11 - December 4, 1920 February 11 (Box 25, Folder 289)
    - Woodrow Wilson and David Lloyd George: draft agreement re: disposition of enemy merchant vessels (copy), 1919 May (Box 25, Folder 290)
    - Memorandum re: "The Saar Valley,", 1919 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 291)
    - H. S. Knapp: "Memorandum concerning the Principles Which Should Govern the Distribution of War Material to be Surrendered by Enemy Powers" (with covering note to Polk), [1919 pre-August 5] (Box 25, Folder 292)
    - [Lester H. Woolsey?]: critique of Knapp's memorandum on the distribution of war material, 1919 August 5 (Box 25, Folder 292)
    - Memoranda and related papers re: reparations for the sinking of German vessels at Scapa Flow, 1919 August 7 - 1920 January 15 (Box 25, Folder 293)
    - La Constitution de l'Empire Allemand du 11 août 1919 (Texte allemand et traduction), [post-1919 August 11] (Box 25, Folder 294)
    - John Foster Dulles: memorandum re: negotiations between France and Brazil about German vessels taken by Brazil, 1919 August 20 (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - British Delegation: declaration of policy of the Allied and Associated Powers re: repatriation of German prisoners prior to ratification (carbon, transmitted by Balfour), 1919 August 27 (Box 25, Folder 296)
    - James B. Scott: memorandum re: Allied response to the German Note of 1919 Sep 5, 1919 September 9 (Box 25, Folder 297)
    - Notes échangées entre le Président de la Conferénce de la Paix et la Délégation Allemande au sujet de l'article 61 de la Constitution Allemande et déclaration relative àl'annulation de l'article 61 de la Constitution Allemande signéeà Versailles le 22 septembre 1919, [post-1919 September 22] (Box 25, Folder 298)
    - Isaac F. Marcosson: memorandum re: economic conditions and the Spartacist movement (copy), 1919 September 25 (Box 25, Folder 299)
    - Charles B. Dyer: "Memorandum on the Political Situation in Germany" (copy), 1919 September 26 (Box 25, Folder 300)
    - Paul M. Warburg: memorandum re: German ability to pay reparations (copy), [1919 pre-October 17] (Box 26, Folder 301)
    - N. A. McCully: memoranda re: miscellaneous naval and maritime matters, 1919 October 26 - November 14 (Box 26, Folder 302)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: the military occupation, 1919 November 1-11 (Box 26, Folder 303)
    - Projet de Lettre au Chargé d'Affaires des Pays-Bas re: decision of the Supreme Council about the disposition of certain German vessels, 1919 November 4 (Box 26, Folder 304)
    - Memoranda re: permitting Germany to collect customs in gold, 1919 November 30, December 8 (Box 26, Folder 305)
    - N. A. McCully: memoranda re: distribution of surrendered naval vessels, 1919 November (Box 26, Folder 306)
    - Lawrence Martin: memorandum re: German political attitudes, 1919 December 3 (Box 26, Folder 307)
    - Van S. Merle-Smith: minutes of meeting re: payment for hire of German ships used in repatriation, 1920 January 27 (Box 26, Folder 308)
    - Norman Davis: draft reply to Senate resolution requesting information about Anglo-American agreements for the disposition of German vessels (carbon), [1920 February 14-18] (Box 26, Folder 309)
    - Cable to the American Mission, Berlin, re: financing food purchase by the German government (draft, copy), 1920 March 26, 31 (Box 26, Folder 310)
    - Charles S. Haight: Brief for the Gans Steamship Line in Support of its Application for relief under Section 20 of AnnexII, Part VIII of the Peace Treaty, 1920 April (Box 26, Folder 311)
    - Financial Clauses ("approved by the Council of Three for insertion in the Peace Treaty with Germany"), undated (Box 26, Folder 312)
    - List, "German Vessels Taken,", undated (Box 26, Folder 313)
  - Great Britain
    - Cecil Arthur Spring-Rice: letter enclosing correspondence and memoranda re: transportation of British subjects in the United States desiring to enlist (originals and copies), 1914 October 14 - 1915 October 2 (Box 26, Folder 314)
    - Courtenay Walter Bennett: letter re: transportation of British subjects in the United States desiring to enlist, 1915 December 30 (Box 26, Folder 314)
    - Robert Lansing: memorandum of conversation with Cecil Spring-Rice re: food imports to Germany (carbon), 1915 May 27 (Box 26, Folder 315)
    - Memo for the Colonel--F.L.P. re: how the British might take advantage of worsening American relations with Germany and Austria, [post-1915 May] (Box 26, Folder 316)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1915-1919 (Box 26, Folder 317)
    - Frank L. Polk and Cone Johnson: memoranda re: discrimination against Hindus in the Burnett Immigration Bill, 1916 July 12-13 (Box 26, Folder 318)
    - Letters and memoranda re: arrest of J. B. Starr Hunt in connection with the steamship "Maverick,", 1916 July 22 - 1917 February 13 (Box 26, Folder 319)
    - Cables exchanged with the American Embassy, London (copies and paraphrase), 1916-1917 (Box 26, Folder 320)
    - R[ichard?] C[rane?]: memorandum of conversation with Spring-Rice, 1917 February 1 (Box 26, Folder 321)
    - Frank L. Polk: draft instruction to the American ambassador in London to request opportunity to decode the original Zimmermann telegram, [1917 Feb] (Box 26, Folder 322)
    - Messages from the Chancellor of the Exchequer (copy and paraphrases of cables from the American Embassy, London), 1917 July 20 - August 2 (Box 26, Folder 323)
    - Alfred Noyes: "In Memory of Cecil Spring-Rice" (copy), [1918 February 14-15?] (Box 26, Folder 324)
    - Press release re: conscription of British and Canadian citizens in the U.S. and U.S. citizens in Great Britain and Canada (mimeo), 1918 March 4 (Box 26, Folder 325)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: American cooperation with the National War Aims Committee, 1918 March (Box 26, Folder 326)
    - Memorandum, "British Credits" (carbon), 1918 July 30 (Box 26, Folder 327)
    - Cables exchanged with the American Embassy, London (copies), 1918-1920, undated (Box 26, Folder 328)
  - Greece
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1915-1918 (Box 26, Folder 329)
    - Memorandum, "Greek Credits,", 1918 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 330)
    - E. K. Vénisélos: Greece before the Peace Congress, 1918 December 30 (Box 26, Folder 331)
    - Carte indiquant les villes & villages incendiés par les Grecs, 1919 February 5 (Box 26, Folder 332)
    - Memoranda and miscellaneous papers re: the Greek occupation of Smyrna, 1919 [May?]-[Oct?] (Box 26, Folder 333)
    - Memorandum re: Bulgarian claims to Thrace, [1919 pre-July 18?] (Box 26, Folder 334)
    - Douglas W. Johnson: memorandum re: "Greek Claims to Bulgarian Thrace,", 1919 July 21 (Box 26, Folder 335)
    - Draft cables to the Secretary of State and cables exchanged with the Secretary of State re: disposition of Thrace, 1919 July 25 - August 31 (Box 26, Folder 336)
    - Memoranda and annotated map re: Anglo-American policy on the Thracian question, 1919 August 7 (Box 26, Folder 337)
    - Douglas W. Johnson: memorandum of conversations with Tardieu, Nicolson, and LeRond re: disposition of Thrace, 1919 August 8 (Box 26, Folder 338)
    - James D. Bourchier: letter enclosing three memoranda re: the Thracian question, 1919 August 12 (Box 26, Folder 339)
    - G. Howland Shaw: memorandum of conversation with Mr. Zarokilli, head of a Greek organization in the United States, re: Greek claims to Thrace, 1919 August 12 (Box 26, Folder 340)
    - Archibald Cary Coolidge: memorandum re: the Tardieu-Venizelos plan for Thrace, 1919 August 14 (Box 26, Folder 341)
    - Bulgarian Delegation: Statement on the Question of Eastern Thrace to the Line of Enos-Midia, [1919 post-August 21] (Box 26, Folder 342)
    - Supreme Council: "Note pour Monsieur Polk" containing observations by Clemenceau, Balfour, and Tardieu re: Greek claims in Greece, Thrace, and Asia Minor (carbon with note of transmittal by Tardieu, translation with covering memorandum), 1919 September 1 (Box 26, Folder 343)
    - "Suggestion d'une solution relative à la Thrace" (copy, translation), 1919 September 4 (Box 26, Folder 344)
    - Cables to the Secretary of State re: Greek claims in Thrace, Greece, and Asia Minor (copies), 1919 September 5-17 (Box 26, Folder 345)
    - Draft of a Treaty between the United States … and Greece, 1919 October 22 (Box 26, Folder 346)
    - Memorandum, "Greece at the Peace Conference" (carbon), [1919 Nov?] (Box 26, Folder 347)
    - "Bulgarian Census [of West Thrace], December 1914, Table IV" (annotated carbon), [1919] (Box 26, Folder 348)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1919-1920 (Box 26, Folder 349)
  - Guatemala
    - Jordan H. Stabler: memoranda of conversations with the Guatemalan minister, 1918 December 18 (Box 26, Folder 350)
    - [Guatemalan Legation, Washington?]: statement of the legal status of the Herrera government, [1920 May?] (Box 26, Folder 351)
    - Cables to the American Legation, Guatemala City (copies), 1920 (Box 26, Folder 352)
  - Haiti
    - Jordan H. Stabler: memorandum of conversation between Polk and the Haitian minister re: interpretation of "collect, receive and apply" in Article II of the Haitian Treaty, 1916 November 2 (Box 26, Folder 353)
    - Cable to the American Legation, Port-au-Prince (copy), 1918 January 26 (Box 26, Folder 354)
    - Breckinridge Long: memorandum re: replacement of the American minister at Port-au-Prince, 1918 December 26 (Box 26, Folder 355)
    - Frank L. Polk: memorandum to Hallett Johnson re: arbitration treaty between Great Britain and Haiti (with pencil reply by Johnson), 1919 April 17-18 (Box 26, Folder 356)
    - Letter and memorandum re: claim of the Haitian American Corporation against the Haitian government, 1919 June 4 (Box 26, Folder 357)
  - Hungary
    - Eugene Pivany, for the Hungarian-American Federation: Rumania in Hungary: Her Conduct during the War, Her Conduct during the "Armistice," Her Territorial Claims, 1919 August 19 (Box 26, Folder 358)
    - Council of the Principal Allied and Associated Powers: draft instructions to the Inter-Allied Commission of Generals at Budapest (carbon), 1919 August 22, [Oct?] (Box 26, Folder 359)
    - Unidentified letter re: appointment of Jews to leading positions in the American army of occupation, 1919 September 26 (Box 26, Folder 360)
    - Allen W. Dulles: memorandum re: testimony of the Hungarian-American Federation before the U.S. Senate Committee on Foreign Relations, 1919 November 6 (Box 26, Folder 361)
    - Map of Hungary Showing Proposed Dismemberment, [1919?] (Box 26, Folder 362)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1919, undated (Box 26, Folder 363)
    - Henry H. Bandholtz: "comprehensive journal and unexpurgated report covering the period from August 5, 1919, to March 6, 1920" (carbon), 1920 March 18 (Box 27, Folder 364)
    - Conditions of Peace with Hungary. English Text, undated (Box 27, Folder 365)
    - Conditions of Peace with Hungary. Conditions of Peace ("English text, uncorrected"), undated (Box 27, Folder 366)
    - Traité de paix entre les puissances alliées et associées et la Hongrie, protocole et declaration. Du 4 juin 1920 (Trianon). Textes français, anglais et italien .), [post-1920 June 4] (Box 27, Folder 367)
  - Interallied Conference
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1917 October 20 - December 31 (Box 27, Folder 368)
  - Ireland
    - Miscellaneous papers re: U.S. citizens in Ireland, 1916 May 12 - July 26 (Box 27, Folder 369)
    - Letters and miscellaneous papers re: Roger Casement and other Irish prisoners, 1916 May 20 - October 12 (Box 27, Folder 370)
    - Lester H. Woolsey: memorandum re: "Status of Irishmen under the proposed conscription agreement with Great Britain" (with letter to which it replies), 1918 March 2 (Box 27, Folder 371)
  - Italy
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1916-1917 (Box 27, Folder 372)
    - [Vincenzo Macchi di Cellere?]: memorandum re: U.S. policy toward Italian purchase of American shipping line, 1917 March 12 (Box 27, Folder 373)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: U.S. policy toward Italian purchase of American shipping line, 1917 March 13-28 (Box 27, Folder 373)
    - Macchi di Cellere: letter to William G. McAdoo re: credits (copy), 1917 July 2 (Box 27, Folder 374)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: shipping, 1917-1918 (Box 27, Folder 375)
    - Robert Lansing: letters to U.S. officials re: increased support for the Italian war effort (carbons), 1918 May 10-29 (Box 27, Folder 376)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: coal supply, 1918 May 10 - September 11 (Box 27, Folder 377)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 378)
    - Memorandum re: blockading of food shipments to the Slavs, 1919 March 10 (Box 27, Folder 379)
    - Memorandum re: recent cables from Rome, 1919 June 20 (Box 27, Folder 380)
    - Memorandum re: recent information about Italian relations with Germany and Hungary, 1919 July 8 (Box 27, Folder 381)
    - Memorandum and cables re: Italian credits, 1919 August 15-28 (Box 27, Folder 382)
    - Arrangement entre les puissances alliées et associées relatif au compte des reparation ence qui concerne l'Italie signé à Saint-Germain-en-Layele 10 septembre 1919 (Textes français, anglais etitalien), [post-1919 September 10] (Box 27, Folder 383)
    - L'Italia alla Conferenza della Pace: Discorsidel Senatore Tommaso Tittoni (Ministro degli Affari Esteri) pronuncia tialla Camera dei Deputati nelli sedute del 27 e 28 settembre 1919, [1919 post-September 28] (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Texts of secret treaties, "The Pact of London," "The Pact of Corfu," the "Pact of Rome" (copies of published versions), undated (Box 27, Folder 385)
  - Japan
    - Memorandum of conversation with Cecil Spring-Rice re: pro-German sentiment in Japan, 1915 December 15 (Box 28, Folder 386)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1915-1918 (Box 28, Folder 387)
    - Edward T. Williams: memorandum re: immigration of Japanese "picture brides,", 1917 April 11 (Box 28, Folder 388)
    - Memoranda of conversations with Japanese officials re: export of shipbuilding materials to Japan, 1917 July 30 - December 27 (Box 28, Folder 389)
    - "Report on the Personnel of the Extraordinary Japanese Mission" (carbon), [1917 post-Jul] (Box 28, Folder 390)
    - Letters and memoranda re: Japanese request for copies of certain papers, 1918 January 9-29 (Box 28, Folder 391)
    - Edward T. Williams: memorandum re: conditions in the South Sea Islands, 1918 January 22 (Box 28, Folder 392)
    - Breckinridge Long: memoranda of conversations with the Japanese chargé d'affaires re: restriction of imports to Japan (carbon, original), 1918 March 9, 30 (Box 28, Folder 393)
    - Letters and memorandum re: Japanese policy toward China, 1918 October 10-18 (Box 28, Folder 394)
    - Breckinridge Long: memorandum to Polk re: "Proposal to ask England to co-ordinate her policy with ours and bring pressure on Japan in Chinese and Siberian matters,", 1918 December 21 (Box 28, Folder 395)
    - Cables exchanged with the American Embassy, Tokyo (copies), 1918 (Box 28, Folder 396)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: shipping, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 397)
    - Frank L. Polk: memorandum to Breckinridge Long re: unattributed Japanese press release, 1919 March 3 (Box 28, Folder 398)
    - Frederick Azro Emery: memorandum re: controversy over Japanese land purchases in Lower California, 1919 April 5 (Box 28, Folder 399)
    - James D. Phelan: press release to Japanese newspapers re: American opposition to Japanese immigration, 1919 July 8 (Box 28, Folder 400)
    - Frank L. Polk: memorandum to Breckinridge Long of conversation with the Japanese chargé d'affaires re: Japanese presence in China (carbon), 1919 July 18 (Box 28, Folder 401)
    - Documents showing Japanese-German collaboration (copies, some in French and German), 1919 September 30 - October 16 (Box 28, Folder 402)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence with the Japanese Embassy, Washington, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 403)
    - Cables to the American Embassy, Tokyo (copies), 1919 (Box 28, Folder 404)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: Japanese-American relations, 1920 February 16-20 (Box 28, Folder 405)
    - "Department's Memorandum Dated March 16, 1920, to the Japanese Embassy in Reply to the Japanese Memorandum of March 2" (copy), 1920 March 16 (Box 28, Folder 406)
  - Korea
    - Memoranda re: cables from the American Embassy, Tokyo, about American nationals in Korea, 1919 April 14 (Box 28, Folder 407)
  - Labor
    - American Federation of Labor: cables to the American Embassy, Petrograd (copies), 1917 June 27 - October 6 (Box 28, Folder 408)
    - William C. Bullitt: memorandum re: "The War Aims of the Inter-Allied Labor and Socialist Conference" (carbon), [1918 post-Feb] (Box 28, Folder 409)
    - Felix Frankfurter: memorandum for Colonel House re: attitude of English and French labor toward the war (carbon), 1918 March 24 (Box 28, Folder 410)
    - Charles Piez: letter to Felix Frankfurter re: war labor policy (mimeo), 1918 September 24 (Box 28, Folder 411)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: Samuel Gompers's mission to Paris, 1918 December 16 - 1919 July 17 (Box 28, Folder 412)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1918-1919 (Box 28, Folder 413)
  - Latin America
    - Second Pan American Scientific Congress: Program of Inaugural Session, 1915 December 27 (Box 28, Folder 414)
    - Frank L. Polk: edited drafts of speech to the Pan American Congress, 1916 January 12 (Box 28, Folder 415)
    - Drafts of the Pan American Treaty and communications on the Brazilian-Chilean counterproposal (mainly carbons), 1916 May 20 - June 16, undated (Box 28, Folder 416)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: W. R. Grace and Co., 1917 August (Box 28, Folder 417)
    - Julius G. Lay: memoranda exchanged with Polk, 1917 December 8 - 1918 July 24 (Box 28, Folder 418)
    - Frank L. Polk: memoranda to Jordan H. Stabler re: conversations with Latin American ministers, 1918 March 7, 28 (Box 28, Folder 419)
    - Memorandum and correspondence re: "Proposed American Mission to certain Latin American countries,", 1918 May 20-31 (Box 28, Folder 420)
    - Pan American Wireless Telephone and Telegraph Company: "Memo Setting Forth Pan American Status" (with routing slip), 1918 October 25 (Box 28, Folder 421)
    - Jordan H. Stabler: memorandum re: Pan American Wireless Telegraph and Telephone Company, 1918 December 2 (Box 28, Folder 422)
    - Jordan H. Stabler: digest, "From Latin American Division, December 4 to 6,", 1918 December 6 (Box 28, Folder 423)
    - Memorandum re: European cable concessions in Latin America, 1919 May 11, 14 (Box 28, Folder 424)
    - Leon Dominian: "Memorandum on Latin American Affairs" extending Jordan H. Stabler's report to the U.S. Commissioners Plenipotentiary of May 27 (with covering letter to Joseph C. Grew), 1919 July 21 (Box 28, Folder 425)
    - Unidentified letter to Norman H. Davis re: the International Gold Clearance Fund Convention, 1920 February 12 (Box 28, Folder 426)
  - League of Nations
    - Commission on the League of Nations: minutes of meetings (mimeo, with attached memoranda on the process of making this record), 1919 February 3-11 (Box 28, Folder 427)
    - Commission on the League of Nations: "Amendments to the Draft of the Covenant Proposed by the Neutral Powers: Meetings of March 20 and 21, 1919" (mimeo), 1919 March 20-21 (Box 28, Folder 428)
    - Report of the Commission on the League of Nations, [1919 April 11] (Box 28, Folder 429)
    - Manley O. Hudson: correspondence with Polk re: the International Labor Conference, 1919 October 2 - November 11 (Box 28, Folder 430)
    - Manley O. Hudson: memorandum of conversation with Harry Osborne Mance re: the Advisory Commission on Ports, Waterways and Railways, 1919 October 10 (Box 28, Folder 430)
    - Memorandum and cable re: convocation of the first meeting of the Council of the League of Nations, [1919 post-November 10], 1919 December 26 (Box 28, Folder 431)
    - Miscellaneous cables, 1919-1920 (Box 28, Folder 432)
    - "Liste des questions à regler" and "Projets" re: the first meeting of the Council of the League of Nations (mimeo), undated (Box 28, Folder 433)
    - Memorandum of remarks (by Woodrow Wilson?) re: attitudes of Europeans and their leaders, undated (Box 28, Folder 434)
  - Liberia
    - Note no. 36 to the American Legation, Monrovia, 1918 March 7 (Box 28, Folder 435)
    - Memorandum re: conversation with Chambrun about the cable connection at Monrovia, 1919 January 7 (Box 28, Folder 436)
  - Lithuania
    - Lithuanian National Council: resolution re: the German proclamation that Lithuania wants to become part of Germany, [1918 March 25?] (Box 28, Folder 437)
    - Lithuanian Commission to the Peace Conference: correspondence re: sending a special mission to the United States, 1919 August 13, 23 (Box 28, Folder 438)
  - Mexico
    - Memorandum, "The Mexican Situation," re: criticism by Senator Fall of U.S. decision not to intervene, [1912 post-July 22] (Box 28, Folder 439)
    - Joshua R. Clark, Jr.: Right to Protect Citizens in Foreign Countries by Landing Forces, 1912 October 5 (Box 28, Folder 440)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1915-1916 (Box 28, Folder 441)
    - Oscar J. Braniff: memorandum, "'Give Mr. Carranza a Chance' is heard from every side, and all patriotic Mexicans are hoping against hope that he will succeed" (carbon, with covering letters), 1916 January 24 (Box 28, Folder 442)
    - Leon Canova: memorandum re: "sixty-seven counts indicating lack of poise of the de facto Government" (carbon), 1916 February 8 (Box 28, Folder 443)
    - Leon Canova: " Confidential Memorandum for use at the conference with the Secretary and the Counselor" re: U.S. support for the Carranza government (carbon), 1916 February 14 (Box 28, Folder 444)
    - Frank. L. Polk: letters re: control of the sisal market by the Comision Reguladora (carbons), 1916 March 9, October 9 (Box 28, Folder 445)